but i do like getting to travel i
wouldn't weird places i felt like during
the pandemic we said yes i was talking
with the other comedians we said yes to
so much stuff we should have said no to
because there's no shows let's make
calls you just go i'm on my way i did a
i did a homeschool convention in florida
y'all
and this was like june of 2020 okay the
pandemic is raging florida's like what
pandemic they're just firing guns at it
will this kill covenant they don't know
but i went i mean i'm the sucker i went
i needed the work i was like let's go
and i didn't know my my agent got me the
job he goes i told him that you were
homeschooled your last two years of high
school i go that's true but how did you
even know he goes it's my job to know
but i go i'm not like today's homeschool
like one out of five families
home schools now that's not how i was
this was 1990s okay when i did it it was
like shut-ins and burn victims and my
family that was the whole school
community
i don't know if i relate to today's home
school but this lady calls me so excited
she's like johnny we're so excited to
have you a thousand homeschool families
are waiting on you now listen you're one
of us you got to write some homeschool
jokes these people love to be teased and
i was like lady i'm on it
and they do not love it
i came running out with my homeschool
jokes it was all i could do to get out
of there alive
y'all want to hear the joke that upset
him
i came around i was like guys what is
the difference between a thousand
homeschoolers and my dogs and they were
like what and i said my dogs are
vaccinated
[Applause]
these homeschoolers will bite you they
will bite you
but i like traveling i remember when i
started out when you start doing comedy
it's the worst because you have to
you're trying to save money anything you
know i stayed in more people's houses
like these club owners or shady they're
like hey don't we're not going to get
you a hotel come stay in the guest room
you're like this
with your creepy family
no it'll be fine and you go in and i
didn't want to say no i don't want to
lose out on the money so you'd go and i
went to this one guy's house and there's
no bed in the guest room
i was like is this a kill room be honest
with me
is this how it ends
he comes back he's holding a duffel bag
he goes i'll blow up this air bed you'll
be good to go anybody slept on one of
these abominations
it sounds like it's going to be amazing
right it's a bed made of air sounds like
you're going to be sleeping on a cloud
you're on this thing five seconds you're
like this is a pool toy i'm on a pool
toy
and i don't know what your experience is
on the air bed but i'm six foot four 200
pounds i'm a big person okay
so the air slowly leaks out of the air
bed overnight you ever have that happen
you wake up you're on the ground the bed
is around you somewhere
right you lay down on a mattress you
wake up in an inflatable shame taco not
cool
you